let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is letter a?",
    answer: "a",
    options: [
      "a",
      "b",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which is the number 1",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "99",
      "z"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is today?",
    answer: "Present",
    options: [
      "Past",
      "Present",
      "Future",
      "Tomorrow"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is the number 3?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "6",
      "9",
      "12"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is the number 4?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "4",
      "44",
      "444",
      "4444"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which is the number 5?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "55",
      "555",
      "5555"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which is the number 6?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "6",
      "66",
      "666",
      "6666"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which is the number 7?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
        "7",
        "77",
        "777",
        "7777"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which is the number 9?",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
        "9",
        "99",
        "999",
        "9999"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which is the number 8?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
        "8",
        "88",
        "888",
        "8888"
    ]
  },
];